It's morning chimes, and it's us.
We are Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku!
Kiki-Umaibar!
Yay!
Yes, this time.
This time, we're going to eat Umaibar with blindfolds on.
and guess what flavor
and guess what flavor of Umaibar it is.
I'd like to do a project.
Yes, sir.
Do you eat Umaibar well?
Maybe not lately.
I don't know, but backstage...
I don't know, but there are some backstage.
That's true.
I'm sure you know the standard ones.
But if you take a closer look...
Beef tongue flavor...
Yakitori flavor...
Even flavors I've never tasted before.
That's right.
Hmm...
Mm-hmm.
Mmm
mmm
Mmm...
It's different, isn't it? There doesn't seem to be anything that tastes like it, and I know what the best ones taste like.
It's okay, isn't it?
I'm sure it's good.
Okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
And so...
I'm going to do it.
What's the motif?
Looks like it.
The rest of it.
I'll put a lock of hair here.
What's that? What's...
What? Something's different.
It's not right.
I'm scared! You know what I mean?
Let's put on the catsuit.
Shoot real!
Let's go get some!
Let's go buy 15 shoot-alikes.
Let's go with this. - What?
What is it? This life.
Maybe I can smell it.
I'm sure.
Something's been placed.
Something's been placed here.
Yes, sir.
It's been a long time.
Question 1.
Bon appétit!
Isn't this takoyaki?
What?
Wait, watch out!
Is this takoyaki?
No, it's not.
I don't know.
No?
No, it's not.
It's okay, right? It's okay to eat it.
Bon appétit.
It's okay to eat it.
Churrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Why?
I'm sure you've had it before.
Isn't this konpota?
The smell, yes.
It's a little expensive, but...
I don't know.
I think it's a little sweeter.
Yes, it is!
It's like a sauce.
That's for sure!
I have no idea!
What's the difference?
Can I just eat the whole thing and see?
He said I can look at it after I eat it.
Then I'll take it and let the white bottle eat it.
Soy!
Sour?
But I've definitely had it before.
Oh, I'll eat it.
He's eating it all.
Okay, bye.
I'll pass out some tissues.
Thank you very much.
Now, if you'll take off your blindfold.
Okay.
But can I look at this?
It's not cod roe.
It's not cheese.
It's not salad.
It's not sugar.
I've eaten so many of these.
Of course you have.
OK, OK, OK.
Easy, easy, easy.
Yes, sir.
No, I don't.
I don't know, I don't know
I don't get it if you say “I don't get it if I say ‘I don't get it’.
Yes, sir.
Now, let's open the floor for Nomoto-san.
Kazami, corn pottage flavor.
Nakayama, octopus dumplings.
The correct answer is
Mentaiko flavor.
What?
Wait a minute.
They recently added a sauce.
They added mentaiko sauce.
It says it's a power-up.
It's true.
It's definitely different.
Definitely not.
Definitely different.
I've had them before.
I eat Umaibo as a compote for sure.
Or cheese.
That's why I think it's compote.
I thought, “I've definitely had this taste before.
I wrote two episodes.
Oh, there you go.
Sauce.
You didn't taste the sauce?
I did, didn't I?
I couldn't think of takoyaki the moment I wrote the second episode.
I couldn't think of anything else.
What, mentaiko?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I've never had mentaiko.
You've had a lot of mentaiko.
Of course you have.
What?
This... this...
This, this.
No, I mean, wait a minute.
It's the most guessable flavor.
Royal road.
It's a classic.
It's very popular.
What?
This is bad.
I'm getting scared.
Thank you very much.
There's a smell on it.
It's so different.
It's sweet.
What is this? What is this?
Compotage.
It's so good!
Oh, it's sweet.
It's like a rusk.
Bon appétit!
Open.
Yum!
What's this? It's delicious!
It's a rusk! I ate it in one bite.
I can't eat it if it's too sweet!
It's a rusk, right?
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry.
This is a little...
Not at all.
Please take off the blindfold.
What's sweet?
Sugar rusks.
It's a masterpiece, but it's a poi...
But if it's possible, it's still possible now and then...
I believe you.
I don't want to be like that in the future.
I don't want to say “no” anymore...
It's so meaningless now...
Okay, Imada, will you please open the floor?
Sugar Rusk for sure!
I didn't expect the combo to be canceled.
The correct answer is...
Sugar Rusk!
Yay!
It's delicious!
Delicious.
But the smell was totally strong
It was sweet.
Yum!
Yay!
It was delicious!
I'm satisfied now.
Delicious!
Next, this way!
Yes!
Natto (fermented soybeans)
I want natto!
Natto is my favorite!
Here it comes!
Here's one.
This one.
Here it is.
It's small. It's a mamayami.
Thank you.
What's this?
Mr. Kayama.
Smells good.
Thank you
Yes.
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Takoyaki!
This is takoyaki.
It's a takoyaki.
I'll say it with a “B”.
This is takoyaki.
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
I don't know.
This isn't it.
What?
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait.
It looks a little bit like mayonnaise.
But it says “Dakudakumayonnaise.
No, it doesn't.
What?
I'm done.
Yeah, I'm done.
Try another one.
I'd like a refill.
I've had a little bit of that before.
It was so cold.
Takoyaki?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Let's take a look.
I'll look.
I'll look. I'll open my eyes.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Oh, my God. Wow.
Shrimp mayo?
But...
Oh, you do?
I felt like there was a lot of mayonnaise.
I think.
Kowayaki
But I've had it before.
Oh, I see.
Wow, shrimp mayo, no, no
I don't think I tasted the shrimp that much.
Me neither.
It tasted like mayonnaise.
Mmm-hmm.
Ehhh...
Takoyaki (octopus dumplings)
Yes, sir.
Let's start with you, Nonaka-san.
I am takoyaki flavor
Oh, Mr. Nakayama, please. Shrimp mayonnaise. Oh, then, Moroka, please. I am takoyaki flavor.
Mr. Nakayama, please. Shrimp mayonnaise.
The correct answer is shrimp mayonnaise.
I've had it too. I can't believe the
Shrimp mayonnaise.
I definitely took a strong quality of the amazing marronnades.
Shrimp
I'll be all over the octopus.
Yay!
Oh, man.
Your mother's...
Zero points.
Two point sixteen.
What is the score of the final question?
Who got this?
I'll give you the inside.
You can have it all.
Yes!
Fourteen.
14 points for the next correct answer.
Pinto?
Pinto? Pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto, pinto.
Pinto. Pinto.
Come on.
Do your job, Pinto.
Pinto.
Is it bad? Not with this taste.
Oh, it's not here.
Oh, here he is.
This is the last one.
Rust.
Thank you very much for the refill.
Thank you very much.
There's powder all around, so you might want to change the surroundings.
That's cool.
It's a takoyaki.
No, it's not.
It's not takoyaki.
You can't feel the sauce on this?
I don't feel the sauce.
It's like ramen noodles.
It tastes like ramen!
Bon appétit!
Mmm?
It tastes so rich and delicious!
I'm going to eat rice, I'm going to eat rice!
White rice, white rice.
Is there some kind of pork cutlet flavor?
But I'm pretty sure it has a lot of meat artifacts in it.
That's for sure.
I see.
Is there anything else?
I think I'll try the side dish.
Did you eat?
Yes, I did.
It's delicious.
Tonkatsu sauce!
Teriyaki Burger
Beef Tongue Salt Yakitori
It doesn't say “salt” on the menu!
Yakitori
Tonkatsu Teriyaki Burger
It's hard to say, isn't it?
Salad Flavor
Salad flavor? I don't think so.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
That's the last thing I want to hear.
What do you mean, like a vegetable salad?
If there is.
I think it's pretty flavorful.
I think it's very strong.
Lastly, Mr. Nakayama would like to make an inquiry.
Ponkatsu sauce!
Mr. Nonaka, please.
Tiriyaki Burger
If you answer correctly, you get 14 points.
The correct answer is...
Tiriyaki Burger... 14 points for a correct answer.
The correct answer goes out...
That's a big turnaround.
It's an upset.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
That's what I'm talking about.
The final point is...
Two points.
14 points.
Yo!
Winner!
I won!
This is hard!
This is hard! I've never had it before.
It was delicious.
But I won!
So...
And last but not least, about you...
Riko, how was it for you?
It's difficult.
I made it all real and made takoyaki.
Isn't this takoyaki?
Takoyaki.
This is takoyaki!
What about you, Rico? No?
You're right. You did say that.
It all smelled really like takoyaki.
I thought it was too sudden.
I'm sure some of them are only available in certain regions.
That makes me want to try all kinds.
I wanted to try the natto flavor.
Can I have the natto flavor first?
I think I'll just take this one.
Well, that's all for now, Kikimai Bo! Thank you so much!
Please subscribe to the channel, click the good button, leave a comment, and leave a notification!
Thank you very much! Bye bye!
This time, I'm going to let the money, the flowers, try.
I'll let you try.
I hope it's not too hard.
Uh, uh, there is.
There's just so many things to mix.
Okay, let's try this one.
There we go. There we go.
Okay, this one.
It's huge.
The color is great. I'll have this one, then. Another one.
Here you go.
Oh, wait.
Yakitori.
Yakitori?
What is it?
It's yakitori. It's yakitori. It's yakitori. It's yakitori.
That's great. - That's great.
What?
Wait a minute.
We're...
I feel like I'm being intimidated.
Go on.
Here we go.
It's low.
There's a lot of it.
I'm so happy.
That's it.
What's this about? Clogs.
Which one? The clogs.
Same.
What do you think?
What's the right answer?
It's a cheap sardine.
Oh, there's no meat in it. Twinkle Twinkle.